movietalkies.com 2019-07-25

# Privacy Policy - Movie Talkies

MovieTalkies.com is an online portal which provides movie related information, database, news, reviews, trailers, pictures, interviews, etc. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using MovieTalkies.com

MovieTalkies.com (“MT”, “us” or “we”) respects the privacy of the visitors to its Website, the home page of which is located at www.MovieTalkies.com (“Website”).

By using or accessing the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE GATHER**

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Website.

When you register with MovieTalkies.com, we will collect your Name, E-mail Address, Phone Number, Gender, Address and Date of Birth. When you save other Personal Information in your account we will collect any such information you enter. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future browsing for you, improving our site, and communicating with you.

**E-mail Communications** : To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Movie Talkies, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our user list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our users.

When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, we will collect your e-mail addresses and any information contained in the e-mail you send us. Once you register with Movie Talkies.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. If you are browsing the Website without registering with Movie Talkies, you are anonymous to us, but we will collect the information listed below, under Personal Information Collected Via Technology

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

**To personalize your experience:** your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

**To improve our Website:** we continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

**To improve customer service:** (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

**To process transactions:** Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

**To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**

**To send periodic emails:** (The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc., which you may opt to unsubscribe by visiting [www.MovieTalkies.com/unsubscribe](http://www.movietalkies.com/unsubscribe-news.html) and entering your email address. MovieTalkies.com will send you a confirmation email on the email address entered which you may confirm by clicking on the link.

**INFORMATION SHARING & DISCLOSURE**

MovieTalkies.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who work on behalf of or with MovieTalkies.com under confidentiality agreements to provide some of the services and features of the MovieTalkies.com community and to help us communicate with MovieTalkies.com members. These service providers may use your personal information to help MovieTalkies.com communicate with you about offers from MovieTalkies.com and our marketing partners. However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information further and/or use it for any other purpose than for MovieTalkies.com.

If you decide to use one of the additional services that are offered by our partners, we may forward Personal Information to these partners to enable them to provide the services that you have requested.

We will disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may disclose information, if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud, situations involving the physical safety of any person, violations of MovieTalkies.com’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by applicable law. If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

Our Website includes third-party advertising and links to other websites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites.

These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION CONNECT VIA TECHNOLOGY**

As you navigate the Website, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our server logs, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Website you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor MovieTalkies.com experience to meet your special interests and needs.

An “Internet protocol address” or “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track your IP Address when you login to the Website including the date and time of login.

Cookies” are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computers hard drive while you are viewing a web site. MovieTalkies.com may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website may not work properly.

Other third parties may place advertisements and cookies on webpages within the MovieTalkies.com network. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MovieTalkies.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the MovieTalkies.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your MovieTalkies.com account. If you would like to opt out of certain messages, log into MovieTalkies.com and go to your account settings by clicking the account link in the top right hand corner. On that page you can edit your preferences.

**CONFIDENTIALITY & SECURITY**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and third parties who we reasonably believe need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. Your MovieTalkies.com account information is protected by a password that you select. MovieTalkies.com uses industry-standard SSL encryption in certain areas of the Website to protect data transmissions. However, no company, including MovieTalkies.com, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

**OTHER SITES**

Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites.

**REGARDING MINORS**

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 18. By accepting the practices in the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use _(_[www.MovieTalkies.com/terms](http://www.movietalkies.com/terms-conditions.html)), you warrant that you are an individual (i.e. not a corporation) and are at least 18 years of age and you have the legal authority to enter into other binding agreements for the purchase and/or use goods and/or Services. You agree to be responsible for use of the Services and access of the Website (as well as for use of our account by others, including without limitation minors living with you).

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [www.MovieTalkies.com/terms](http://www.movietalkies.com/terms-conditions.html)

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

MovieTalkies.com may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MovieTalkies.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our Website. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Website. Continued use of our Website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
